// /mock/resultCard.ts
export const cardData = [
  {
    front: '테스트1',
    back: '경준이형',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },
  {
    front: '테스트2',
    back: '사랑해',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },
  {
    front: '테스트3',
    back: '보고싶어',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },
  {
    front: '테스트1',
    back: '경준이형',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },
  {
    front: '테스트2',
    back: '사랑해',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },
  {
    front: '테스트3',
    back: '보고싶어',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },{
    front: '테스트1',
    back: '경준이형',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },
  {
    front: '테스트2',
    back: '사랑해',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },
  {
    front: '테스트3',
    back: '보고싶어',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },{
    front: '테스트1',
    back: '경준이형',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },
  {
    front: '테스트2',
    back: '사랑해',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },
  {
    front: '테스트3',
    back: '보고싶어',
    containerClassName: 'h-80 w-48',
    frontClassName: 'bg-blue-200 text-black',
    backClassName: 'bg-blue-400 text-black',
  },
];
